emis.gov.bd 2018-09-04

# Privacy

**Privacy Policy & Terms of Use**  
---  
Online Privacy is a constantly evolving landscape and DGHS plans to take all reasonable efforts to maintain up to date and effective online privacy standards and practices. We have linked every page of our web site to this page for your convenience and you may also contact us at info@synesisit.com with any questions or concerns that you may have.   
**What Personal Information We Gather**  
We will ask you when we need information that personally identifies you (personal information) or allows us to contact you. The personal information we collect may include your name, title, company or organization name, e-mail address, phone number, work or home address, information about your job function, information about your company, etc.   
**How We Use It**  
We gather personal information that we need to know when you ask over to do something for you. For example, if you ask us to send you our quarterly newsletter, product information, etc. we need to know and store your email address. We will always ask for your permission and inform you how we're going to use your personal information first. You can always choose not to provide it.   
**Here the other uses of your information:**  
To contact you regarding other products and services which may be of interest to you (including those we may offer jointly with other companies). At any time, however, you may opt out of such contact. To fulfill your requests by us or by others involved in fulfillment. To contact you for customer satisfaction surveys, market research or in connection with certain transactions. By DGHS and selected organizations for marketing purposes if you have permitted such use. We maintain a strict "No-Spam" policy that means that we do not sell, rent, or otherwise give your e-mail address to a third-party, without your consent or as permitted by this Privacy Policy.   
**Third-Party Sites**  
The Site may contain links to other sites. DGHS is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such sites. Users and visitors will need to check the policy statement of such other sites to understand their policies. Users who interact with such sites may be sharing their private information with such site. It is the user's responsibility to keep such information private and confidential.   
**Privacy Policy Changes**  
DGHS reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time. DGHS will post any changes here so that our users will know what information DGHS gathers, how it might use that information and whether it will disclose such information to anyone.   
**Questions**  
If you have questions about this Privacy Policy, please send e-mail to info@dghs.gov.bd
